this Friday unfixable Friday's are live
board meeting we are discussing micro
solidarity on reading micro solidarities
site one of the articles and I don't
know where it is to be able to refined
it is about this space or my
interpretation of it is there's this
space between I need to solve my own
problems by myself I need to have
sovereignty I need to learn how to grow
all my own food how to forge weapons and
tools and like I need to know it all I
need to do it all and they need to fix
this for me right so it's either you're
in it by yourself or the government the
corporation someone else needs to change
something and and do it for us
there is a huge space in between that
and that is the space that together Tech
is working in how do you bring the
individuals together to empower them to
create their own solutions so they're
not by themselves and they're not
leaving it up to the giant other the
giant and them there's a city base in
between I and them that we can solve
problems in and the only way to solve
problems in that space is to make them
diverse to make them to take a step back
and look at the big picture and how do
we empower people the individuals in
that big picture so we don't get to look
at the statistics as much as they might
totally line line it out and say oh look
everyone has to go vegan that is a rule
that we don't have the authority to
impose what we can do is ask how are you
eating in what's that impact having on
you your body you earth people how can
we create something together that helps
you eat better it helps you improve your
life and the impact you're having on
other people and it's still not for us
it's still an invitation so how can we
get your diet better right not
necessarily better under my guidelines
better under yours and empowering people
with those tools that space between I
and them is where we solve the problem